She had no one to play with for thirty years.
Full Circle is a drama, horror, mystery film directed by Richard Loncraine.
After the death of her daughter, wealthy housewife Julia Lofting abruptly leaves her
husband and moves into an old Victorian home in London to re-start her life.
All seems well until she is haunted by the sadness of losing
her own child and the ghosts of other children.
Julia Lofting, played by Mia Farrow.
Magnus Lofting, played by Keir Dullea.
Mark Berkeley, played by Tom Conti.
Lily Lofting, played by Jill Bennett.
David Swift, played by Robin Gammell.
Heather Rudge, played by Cathleen Nesbitt.
Full Circle, released in the United States as The Haunting of Julia, is a 1977 supernatural
horror film directed by Richard Loncraine, and starring Mia Farrow and Keir Dullea.
Based on the novel Julia by the American writer Peter Straub, it is the first film realisation of one of his books, and follows a
woman who, after the death of her daughter, finds herself haunted by the vengeful ghost of a young girl in her new home.
A co-production between Canada and the United Kingdom, the film was shot in London, and first released under the
title Full Circle, opening at the San Sebastián International Film Festival in September 1977.
It was subsequently released theatrically in England and Canada in May 1978,
through Cinema International Corporation and Astral Films, respectively.
The film went unreleased in the United States until May 1981, when it was given theatrical
distribution through Discovery Films under the title The Haunting of Julia.
The film received mixed reviews from critics at the time of its release, with some praising its
atmosphere and performances, while others deemed it either predictable or too plodding.
The film explores themes of london, england, based on novel or
book, loss of loved one, haunted house, haunting.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.